So Many Mr. Wrongs. So Few Mr. Rights.
Broken English is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Zoe Cassavetes.
Nora Wilder is freaking out.
Everyone around her is either in a relationship, married, or has children, while she's in her
thirties, alone with job she's outgrown and a mother who constantly reminds her of it all.
Not to mention her best friend Audrey's "perfect marriage".
But after a series of disastrous dates, Nora unexpectedly meets Julien, a
quirky Frenchman who opens her eyes to a lot more than love.
Nora Wilder, played by Parker Posey.
Audrey Andrews, played by Drea De Matteo.
Mark Andrews, played by Tim Guinee.
Vivien Wilder-Mann, played by Gena Rowlands.
Julien, played by Melvil Poupaud.
Nick Gable, played by Justin Theroux.
Broken English is a 2007 American romantic comedy-drama film written and
directed by Zoe Cassavetes, in her feature directorial debut.
The film stars Parker Posey, Melvil Poupaud, Drea de Matteo,
Justin Theroux, Peter Bogdanovich, and Gena Rowlands.
Broken English had its world premiere at the Sundance Film Festival on January 20, 2007
and a limited theatrical release in the United States on June 22, 2007.
The film was nominated for two Independent Spirit Awards: Best Female
Lead for Posey and Best First Screenplay for Cassavetes.
The film explores themes of career woman, single, woman director.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.